## KEVIN D. DUMAS

# 9708 W Capitol Drive · Milwaukee, WI 53222

## Kevin.dumas@yahoo.com • 414-484-9513

Certified Forklift Operator and Machine Operation Specialist with over 13 years of experience seeking to enhance my career step with a respected company. Detail-oriented who exemplifies professionalism and the ability to manage multiple projects and tasks at any given moment. Exemplary leadership qualities and the ability to work with people from varying backgrounds, while implementing team values. *Core competencies include:* 

- Independent
- Strongly Driven
- Well Organized
- Punctual
- Safety Management
- Warehouse Operations
- Knowledgeable

### CAREER EXPERIENCE

# Eaton Corporation, Pewaukee, WI. 09/2017 - Present

### Machine Press Operator

- Possess physical stamina and strength for lengthy standing periods
- Safely and appropriately operate CNC equipment
- Utilize and monitor computer controls to produce quality, completed products
- Translate instructions into computer commands to perform the correct functions
- Complete quality checks and paperwork every day to maintain accurate production

# 618 Live on Water, Milwaukee, WI. 03/2009 - 10/2017

## Security Lead

- Approached incidents in a controlled and calm, professional manner
- Implemented and maintained safety according to the policies of the establishment
- Created accurate administration records of any security related incident
- Engaged in immediate action in the event of a major incident or occurrence

# Rockwell Automation, Mequon, WI. 08/2015 - 08/2016 // BuySeasons, New Berlin, WI. 04/2014 - 07/2015 Forklift Operator/Material Handler

- Supported warehouse operation workflows by receiving and shipping, loading and unloading goods
- Utilized heavy machinery and equipment, including palletizers, forklifts, high pickers, and pallet runners and jacks
- Maintained workflows and production schedules in alignment with company policies and federal regulations
- Provided training to new employees in forklift operations to help them obtain certification

# Metal Ware Distribution, Manitowoc, WI. 02/2008 - 02/2009 // Federal Mogul, Manitowoc, WI. 06/2010 - 07/2011 Shipping Clerk/Chrome Plate Operator

- Displayed the ability to accurately read and interpret simple instructions such as safety rules, operating and maintenance instructions, and procedure manuals
- Strategic-relationship/partnership building skills listened attentively, solved problems creatively, and used tact and diplomacy to find common ground and achieve "win-win" outcomes
- Commended for initiative, enthusiasm, intense customer focus and dependability in performance evaluations

### **EDUCATION**

Forklift Operation Certificate (2012) Frayser High School Diploma (1995)

References Available Upon Request